[ED.
Seino, this is Angulum.
I would like to introduce our new single, "Ai no Kedamono" (released on June 14) and the music video for the song "Dousounyu".
Yay!
I would like to start with Alumni.
Okay, let's go. Go ahead!
Oh.
Hey, it's like a movie.
It's like a road show.
Yoo-hoo!
I love it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Does this really work?
Does it really work?
This is, uh, right over there.
That's where the table is, right there.
Oh!
It's so cute!
So cute!
Amazing wind!
Cute~
It's sunny.
It's so nice.
It's amazing. What's going on?
It's so cute!
It's fun.
It's cute.
Nice sunny weather.
Like the reflection in the trees.
Beautiful.
It's reflected in the trees.
It was cloudy.
Pretty.
The red one,
It's the one I ate.
The one that ate a lot.
It's cute.
Doesn't this look homemade?
Yes, it does.
It's cute.
It's cute. They're all cute.
They're cute.
Cute.
It was an example starting with "L".
It's LAY.
Cute.
Nekiresia.
Love.
Nice.
The wind is blowing and the pin hasn't stopped this time.
Seriously.
Two scares in a row are not right.
My head is being ripped out of my ass.
Fear.
It's rough. Rough.
It's so cute.
Cute.
It's coming out.
What are you doing now?
He's so cute.
It's Lay.
It's cute.
It's so yellow.
A paw.
Left bender is on the swing.
It's LAY.
It's cute.
What's that?
It's a nice mural.
It's cute.
It's really good.
You can really see it.
I just walked so hard.
How many times did you take this picture?
Cute.
So cute.
That was fun.
Flowers.
The sunset is nice.
Amazing.
It's great.
It's so good.
Dance, dance, dance, dance!
So cute!
Diamond
It's great!
I love it!
Nice, so red!
Dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance, dance.
Dance dance dance dance
I'm tired of crying.
I forgot. That I was crying.
I'm not getting so good.
Oppe, do you want to cry?Oh, Oppe, you're going to cry.
Oh no.
Oh Pei, you're going to cry.
The sun looks good on you.
He's so cute.
You're in a groove.
What's that?
No, it's not.
Did you pull it out?
Oh!
Oh, that's good.
Wow.
That's great.
No, no, no.
I'm kind of impressed.
Amazing.
I cried inside.
It's all just one person.
Only Ue-chan.
Take-chan.
Like the introduction.
What the hell is this?
Take-chan.
OK.
Not yet.
Kiria.
Is that a long time ago?
That's it. That's it, isn't it?
What was it?
The interview.
Interview?
Yes, that's right. It's a comment.
Oh, that's right.
Rica was moment 2.
Good!
Great!!!
That's great!
He really wanted me to write this in English, but I wrote it in katakana.
I say as I say it.
Tell him to write it himself,
It's the same as usual.
Oh! The moment he says "ah! the moment he says "Aha!
Aha! It's totally different.
It's totally different.
It's the guy.
Yay!
It's so good!
Super cute!
So cute.
It was so good.
It's wonderful.
Thank you very much.
Watch it again and again.
Tage-chan.
Absolutely impossible. Absolutely impossible.
Tage-chan. Tage-chan.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.